Okay. So, it's saying that it's done
that pass and everything is good. I just
wanted to ask it to explain itself about
this requirements.ext. Can you explain
why you needed a requirements
text? I thought we were using UV.
Okay, let's see what it says.
UV still needs an input requirements.
Okay, that's fine. That's fine. So it
did I I if you know about UV, it didn't
set up a UV project, which is what I
would have done. It used
requirements.ext, but it was still using
UV. It claims at least maybe I should
check that. Uh but uh I I I think that
sounds fine. Um if we look here, we
should see the Docker file. This Docker
file is the the the is this is where you
describe the Docker image. If you
remember when I when I explained how
Docker works and you can look through
this to see that it's using Python 312
uh which is always a sensible idea for
this kind of stuff. It's uh yep it's
brought in the requirements text and yes
it it has indeed done that's not the
best way of doing it for people that
know UV but it doesn't matter. That's
fine. It works for this purpose. I'm
happy with that. Okay, good. Um now
maybe I can ask it. Please, please tell
me how I test
the part myself.
Okay, so we'll get it to explain to us
how we can check that part two is
working cuz we want to uh uh trust but
verify at each step. Okay, so it's
saying first of all that we should bring
up a terminal. Here's a here's a
terminal right here. I can press the
plus button to have a terminal and I
should go to run um scripts start
mac.Sh.
So I'm going to do scripts
startm.sh.
And it says permission denied because I
need to um hang on. No, I'm just going
to I'm just going to uh I I know what to
do, but I rather than uh do anything,
I'm just going to show this
allow. So if you have a problem like
that, you just tell it the problem and
it should fix it. And now it's telling
me to do that again. So now I'm going to
do So I'm going to go over to my
terminal. Just here is where you flip
between the different terminals you have
open. I'm going to run
scripts/startmac.sh.
That's the script that should be
starting this. Up it goes. It has. It
has started. And now it's telling me
that I should go to localhost colon 8000
to see this. And that's what we'll do.
Okay. So I'm going to go to localhost
colon 8000
sorry localhost 8000 slash and here we
go.
Uh try slashhalth
and status is okay. and try slash API
slashhello
hello from fast API everything is
working thank you thank you to our
GitHub copilot part two is working okay
and now it's telling us that we can run
the stop script I know as well I can
just dot control c and that will work
perfectly well too okay um that's good
part two is done
Are all the success
criteria
for part two achieved?
Let's see what it says. Not fully. We
verified we did not measure 80%
coverage. Um
uh let me see or validate scripts on PC
or Linux. Well, I'm not going to be
using PC Linux for this. So, um I'm good
to skip that the
PC Linux
and I can confirm
I've tested all the roots.
Let's mark that complete
and proceed with part three.
On it goes. So, let's go and have a look
uh and have a look at remind ourselves
what part three is all about. But I
imagine this is going to be an exciting
moment for us when we actually get to
see a proper front end. Uh let's go into
the docs. Let's go into plan. Uh let's
open preview
and see what part three it is indeed.
Adding in a front end, a static front
end. You can notice over here that it's
showing us that there are 16 files
changed and it shows you the sort of
edits the diffs and this is where you
can see what what differences are
happening like what what uh what is
being changed by the the uh the agent
and see what's what's uh um what's being
added what's being removed and so on and
pressing the keep button means that
you're saying I agree to those diffs and
there's a school of thought that says
that you should look through every
single diff individually we're not going
to do that I'm just pressing the keep
button we're going to accepting changes
like that unless there's something that
we're particularly concerned about like
maybe when we first use the the AI
aspect. All right. Anyway, I will see
you back in a second when part three is
ready for testing. I'm going to stop for
a moment while it's in the middle of
thinking. It's been going for about 10
minutes to mention something interesting
that I'm seeing happening here. I I made
the perhaps I'll keep allowing things as
they go. made perhaps a foolish point of
saying that it had to achieve 80% unit
test coverage and it's been spending the
last like most of the time it wrote the
stuff very quickly. It's been bogged
down in testing building long
complicated tests to try and get to make
sure that it's covered things but it's
not doing it in an intelligent way. It's
not testing things that really matter.
It's adding in tests just for the sake
of it that are testing things in a way
that that that are not not considered
helpful way to test things just in order
to achieve the objective. And this is a
great example of a trap that you can
fall into with LLMs that they're so
eager to follow the the letter of the
rules that they don't push back and say,
you know what, I know you wanted 80%
test coverage, but we're not making
productive use of time. So So that's
something to note. Now it says
everything is done. It's done lots and
lots of testing. It's been spending most
of the time testing. It's done both
front end and backend tests. So, we
should now be in really good shape. It's
time for us to try out part three. Okay.
So, with part three completed, we're
going to give it a test. I'm going to do
the start Mac script. You should be
doing a start PC script. Up it comes.
The server has come up. It's running.
So, now I should bring up my browser and
go to localhost.
localhost
colon 8000.
And we are hoping to see a camban. We do
see a cambban. Here we have it. This is
the camban. The front end is being
served. It looks great. We should be
able to move that over there. Yes, we
can. We have a camb front end view.
Looking very fancy indeed. The good old
Codeex one that we like so much. Cambban
Studio. All right. I'd say that that's
that's success. It's time to move
forwards. I'm going to say approved.
move to part four. By the way,
going forwards,
please update the plan
to only uh uh achieve 80% test coverage
if it's sensible
to do so. Avoid adding unnecessary
tests just to hit 80%.
Focus on useful on valuable uh on on
valuable tests.
Not hitting 80% is okay.
All right, let's uh give it that
direction. That's a good rest that maybe
will help us out later on. But now it's
moving on. It's going to step four. I
will see you in a minute when we have
that done. And while it's running, I'll
just mention again, looking here at
these diffs. You see the green are the
new lines it's adding. The red is where
it took something out because it
replaced it with that. You can press
keep and undo on each of these diffs
manually. Or I can just come here and
press keep here and everything is
accepted. And uh you know, as uh Andre
would say, watch it like a hawk. But I
think you probably don't need to review
all of the diffs at this point, just the
sensitive ones that that you really care
about. And I'm going to uh definitely
allow for that. I'll see you in a
minute. Okay, it says that part four is
complete. We'll be the judges of that.
We'll come back over here. Uh where are
we exactly? We are just in the PM
directory. So, I'm going to start
scripts slash start_mac.
Oops, sorry. Where am I? Start-mac.sh.
Let's give this a whirl. And now we will
take a look and see what we have
running. Up we come. We're going to
reload this page. Oh, it's still
starting up. Sorry. There we go. I was
for a moment I I was uh I was concerned.
Uh so, welcome back. Sign in to continue
your Camban board. Use the demo
credentials. Sign in with user and
password. Oops. Spell it right though.
There we go. Sign in. And in we come.
Yeah. So, Google of course does not like
that. I'm not going to add that to Last
Pass. Ah, up comes my Camban Studio. And
there's a log out button up there. And
if I press that, I come back to here.
That's nice. This seems to be working
just fine. I like that a lot. In we have
this here. Okay, that's going to be
annoying, isn't it? Uh, very good. Okay,
I'm uh I'm happy with that. Um, and uh
now log out and log in.
And here we go. And did you see that?
Look at that. This is uh this is
maintained. That is good to see.
Excellent. Okay. All right. So now I'm
going to do control C to stop that
server running. Now something I'm going
to do now that I said I was going to do
every step and I didn't. So you did did
you notice? Did you Did you uh stop me?
Uh something that I said I would do is
be taking git snapshots as we go, which
we should be doing. But you know, the
first four four parts have been pretty
innocuous. We could always do them
again. And then they were low risk. But
now we're going to get to databases
coming up. It's a little bit more
serious. So, it's a good point. Uh, so,
so if you don't know the basic git
commands to do this kind of thing, then
please that do do or there's some some
git resources that I've got, but also
you could just ask ask the agent or ask
chat GPT just to give you the basics.
But essentially, I could type get status
to see all of the things that have
changed. A lot of things have changed. I
can do get add dot to stage them all.
For commit, I can do get commit minus m
part for complete. And that is now all
put committed to the repo just to my
local repo. I haven't pushed it to
GitHub, but I've committed it locally in
a way that I could then come back to
this point if I need to. That's a good
practice. Okay, on to part five.